Jean.
Jeanie.
If you get this, it means...
Well,
you already know what it means.
I can't imagine what
they're going to say about me.
And I know
you're going to believe it.
Which is okay.
I mean, I already
put you through so much.
I only hope...
I only hope you can forgive me.
But please, Jeanie,
and I know you're not
going to want to do this.
You must publish
my research, everything.
And if the journals
won't take it, I mean,
just, just give it away.
Put it online, just
some place people can find it.
I know you think I'm delusional,
but you must do this for me.
You must.
Anyway.
If you do this I...
I think I could be at peace.
I love you.
I'm sorry.
[pained grunt]
[ominous music plays]
[pop music plays]
[song lyrics] I have been
waiting for this all my life
I was a worm
and now I am a butterfly
I'm going
through it all like, 1, 2, 3
Is someone waiting
for someone like me?
You're getting high
I'm getting so fucked up
I wanna dance
with all the lights turned up
I made a wish into
the bottom of a well
Got you under my spell
Ohhhhhhhh Yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
Oooooooh
Ohhhhhhhh Yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
Oooooooh
[phone ringing]
Hey, Mom.
Did you mean to call?
Oh, hi. Hi.
You're on the--
You're on the camera thing. Hi.
I just was calling to make sure
that you have a cover for
the weekend.
You know,
I could drive up and help--
No. No, I've got it, we're fine.
- How was that interview you did?
- It wasn't a...
I'm starting a company.
- Another one?
- We've been over this.
It's not another app, is it?
I mean, how do you even make
money from those things,
aren't they free?
It's a complicated...
But you never even studied
computers.
I'm more on
the business side, Mom.
You didn't study business
either. I don't understand.
- It's really hard these days--
- Mom.
...to survive on one income.
- It won't be one income...
- And with that house, my God...
I shouldn't have cosigned
that loan--
If either of those had
gone to market--
way too much money,
and it doesn't even
have a third bedroom.
Wait honey,
what's-- what's wrong?
Are you okay? Oh.
Oh. My sensitive boy.
I have to go feed Mikey.
Okay.
Christopher...
You don't cry like
that in front of Sharon right?
Because despite what
all these new wave feminists say
- women really want a strong man.
- Bye, Mom.
[baby crying]
[song lyrics]
You wanna get me like that
I'm just a sucker for love
- I wanna know you like that
-  [phone dings]
I'm just a sucker for love
Look at this DILF.
You look good, Bro. Look at you.
- Yeah. Say hey.
- [baby crying]
Hey, there's the man of
the house, cute little fucker.
I might need a drink too.
Don't stress, Bro.
It's all just temporary.
You got to think of it
more like a solo vacay,
you know,
a little sexual tune up,
get somebody
to check under your hood,
check the oil if
you're into that sort of thing
so you can be refreshed
and focused for Sharon.
Saved my marriage, many times.
You're divorced.
You're a dick.
Dude, really? The camera cover?
Nobody's trying to watch
you jerk off, you jerk off.
Come on, snap snap.
Share your screen.
What do we got?
Yeah, that's
your panty dropping pic?
Who are you trying
to fuck? Mormons?
I look good there.
Ugh.
Dude, this is
fucked. Open your iCloud.
Don't blame me.
Chop chop, man.
Let me see them dick pics.
- Jesus, man.
- I know, I know. Power through.
Just close
your eyes. Scroll down.
I got it. Scroll down.
Down.
Ansel Adams, what's
with all the nature photography?
- Will you just--
- Wait!
Scroll that shit back up.
Oh. Oh, yes.
- I should start jogging again.
- Camping photos, bro.
So rugged,
so approachable. I love it.
Beautiful. Make it public.
I don't know, man.
You and Sharon are separated.
You're not doing anything wrong.
I know, man. But, like,
what if I match with this, like,
hot twenty-something year old,
right? And I lose perspective?
I gotta think about Mikey,
too now.
I just... Just for me,
I would like to clarify...
That your concern
is that you're going to be
so irresistible
to all the hot,
young tail out there?
Look, can we just do this
another weekend
when I don't have my child?
My guy, I love you.
But my worry is that
if we put this off,
you're going to start projecting
even more sad sack,
broken man vibes.
Chicks dig confidence.
Fun, strong.
We got to hit a window
where we can pretend you're
at least one of those things.
- It's only a trial separation.
- Oh, my God.
Please? Please.
- Okay.
- Don't you tease...
- Yes, okay, fine.
- Do it. Fucking do it.
Yeah!
Shut up! Wooh!
Fucking swipe. And
honestly, dude, just all rights.
You don't have to meet with
them. Just get some matches.
Standards low right now.
Don't let me see you go
fucking left. Right.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
[Eddie] When Charlisse and
I were first talking about
having kids,
and the idea
the idea, mind you,
of a sperm donor came up.
Yeah, sure.
So, Harry, he raised her, but
he's not her biological father.
Okay.
So Patty thought it would be
a good idea
if we got the sperm
donation from Harry.
- Oh. Oh, God.
- Yeah.
And she said it all like,
"“oh, well, you know..."”
"“Harry never got to
have kids of his own..."”
Like that's not the most
fucked situation ever.
Charlisse literally
turkey basting--
Oh, god.
- her step-dad's splooge and--
- Don't say that.
- fucking jamming it up--
- Oh, oh, oh shit.
What?
That was...
that was someone we know.
Shit. Yeah, that's Karoline.
- She goes to our gym.
- Does she know Sharon?
They talk on the ellipticals.
Bro, she's pretty hot.
Fuck, fuck! Fuck man.
Calm down. Just undo the match.
I don't know how to do that.
Just unmatch.
You hit the chat icon.
I don't see the chat icon.
The chat icon.
It's right at the...
Top right of your screen, man.
There's nothing
in the top right...
It looks like
the bobble-head sperm.
- There's no bobble head sperm.
- The circle is the bobble-head
You're just making
things up now.
The fucking international
symbol of chat!
I'm just gonna
delete the account.
She already saw it.
You might as well just
delete the photos,
change the profile.
There's unmatch. There it is.
Maybe she was swiping fast
like me and didn't notice?
Absolutely.
That smoke show was definitely
just saying yes to everyone
for sure.
[computer dings]
Oh dude, ignore her.
She's got no evidence.
[computer dings]
Deny, deny, deny.
Shaggy that shit. "“Wasn't me."”
How did this happen?
Fucking algorithm,
probably knows you guys go to
the same gym.
I wasn't even
going to do anything.
- Fucking algorithm... Oh.
- [doorbell rings]
- My food's here, sorry.
- Dude.
What? It's a gray area.
You guys are separated.
We have only been
separated for two weeks.
- Hey, I tipped on the card.
- Eddie!
Hey, man, don't shut me out.
I can help. Don't you do that--
[phone ringing]
Fuck.
Is everything okay?
I was just on
my phone and I'm...
- I'm not sure what you did but--
- I didn't do anything.
I was trying to log in the app.
It's not working.
Oh. The baby monitor?
Yeah.
But... Did
you change the log in or?
I couldn't remember if
it was your old work email or...
Yeah, the company
email isn't active anymore.
I sent you that link, remember?
To the feed?
Yeah.
No, it's, it's funny.
I got a feeling,
you know how I get a feeling.
I think it's called paranoia.
Not if you're right.
- Well, we're fine.
- Okay.
- I'm fine.
- Good.
- How's the party?
- [crowd cheering]
It's been very
day-drinking.
That sounds like fun.
I'm not as good at
day drinking as you are.
Oh.
Hey, Chris.
- Everything good?
- Hey, Charlisse.
We're fine. We're fine.
Okay. I'm just checking.
It's just, you know, Nellie's
bachelorette party so you know,
this whole situation.
Okay. I'm just checking.
You're your own
woman tonight, Sherry-baby.
Chris, stop smothering her.
- I...
- He is not trying to smother,
I'm trying to mother.
Okay, well, you're not
a mother tonight either.
You're a bad bitch.
I'm a bad bitch. Okay.
- Thank you, Cherrie.
- Okay.
How's our bad bitch baby?
He's good, he's sleeping.
You can trust me.
Okay.
No I...I know.
It's just
I'm sorry that I got so upset
when I dropped him off.
- It's just--
- No, I'm sorry.
That was my fault.
With Nellie and Jake
getting married while we're...
They have what we used to have.
We can get it back.
Maybe, I don't know.
Maybe.
So...
You can talk tomorrow?
Yeah.
No, um...
Maybe, I...
Let's talk when
I'm thinking straight.
Okay, but that's okay. I'm...
- Heyyy.
- Don't--
You gotta rest your eyes.
You know how they get
when you're stressing out
on screens all day.
[Charlisse] Come on,
there's a party!
Okay, I gotta go. Bye.
I love you.
Alright, I love you.
[opens beer]
[mysterious music begins]
[error sound effect]
[message alert]
[mysterious music builds]
Oh, fuck.
[message alert]
[call ringing]
Hey.
Uh...
Why not?
I lost my voice.
Oh.
Is... is it weird
that I'm talking and you're not?
Can you turn the filter off?
Kind of want to see your face.
Don't want to
pressure you or anything.
Okay.
Maybe...
Just take off glasses.
Are you a Russian bot?
[laughs]
I don't know, like...
This could be all prerecorded.
Like, how do
I know that this is real?
Sure. You could be some, like,
four hundred pound dude
in a basement, you know
Clicking buttons
that program your responses.
How?
Do...
the Vulcan salute.
No, you gotta...
Nice.
Okay.
Um...
Let me see your...
tattoos.
[hypnotic music begins]
Those are cool.
What do they mean?
On your legs. Show me those.
Looks like it feels good.
I will choose to
believe you for now.
I don't know to...
rip people off.
Which...
I mean I guess,
if that's what this is,
you should cut your losses now,
because I'm broke.
No, I'm fine.
Things could be better, sure.
Ahh...
Yeah. Why not?
We didn't hit a goal
for this company I co-founded,
and so we're not going to get
the next round of investment.
I have a lot of debt,
like, a lot, so... Seriously, if
if this is a scam,
let me save you the time.
I don't want to ruin
your credit score too.
Mm. The jury's
still out on that too.
I'm married.
Did you know that?
Well... separated.
Maybe.
I don't know.
And a dad.
A dad who's sitting here
talking to you instead of...
Spending time
with his kid. So...
What does that say about me?
That you're human.
Thanks.
Yeah, that's what I keep
trying to tell myself. That...
I'm only human.
I've been going
crazy with
the stress of the business.
You know, my...
My eyes started twitching
Like I'd be writing my
thousandth email,
looking for
someone to bail us out.
And just like
twitch, twitch, twitch.
Couldn't even read
what I'd written on the screen.
I hope you're right.
I guess it's just...
So hard to find balance.
You know, and when I was
working all the time, Sharon,
My ex, would come over and...
Put her hands on my eyes
and just say,
"“Breathe."”
But at the end,
it was just like, I can't.
I don't have time.
And now all I have is time.
And I still can't get out
of my head and into my body.
Sorry.
This was really stupid. I'm--
I'm embarrassed.
Uh... Wow...
Can you turn off the filter?
Just for a minute?
Wow.
Oh, come on.
Yeah, I like you.
Of course. Yeah.
Uh, where?
[message alert]
[mouse clicking]
Yeah, no joke
When?
Now.
Give me a minute.
[call ringing]
[panting] Chris, give it to me.
Give me
your Social Security number.
And your mother's maiden name.
Oh, and your high school mascot.
She asked me to come over.
Wow, that's fast.
There... There
is no way I can go.
- That's your fear talking.
- Correct.
Fear of living life.
Fear of being murdered.
Oh, that's just silly.
Dudes don't get
murdered via dating apps.
They get blackmailed.
You always
know just what to say.
- Show me her profile.
- [message alert]
- Dude.
- I know, right?
- [computer alert]
- No.
Dude.
You matched with her, too.
Yeah. Yesterday.
Now I know she's full of shit
because I'm way cuter and
she didn't message me.
That's weird,
though. I don't see a link.
- Yeah. How would that work?
- [message alert]
I don't know.
Multiple profiles maybe.
Trying to lure
horny Instagram followers?
You know, she doesn't
link to an Instagram.
Hm. True.
So what? You gonna go?
- Want me to watch Mikey?
- No, man.
I can't.
- What? I...
- [message alert]
Right, right, right, right.
You got that thing
that's wrong with you.
What's that thing called?
A conscience?
That's the word.
Well listen, man.
I'm fucking shit-housed.
I'm gonna pass out.
All right, night.
Night.
Lights on.
[electrical surge]
- [glass breaks]
- Jesus.
[front door creaks open]
[wind howls]
[door closes]
[broken glass rattles]
[mysterious music plays]
[photo shutter sound]
- [club music]
-  [app alert]
[app alert]
[message alert]
[hypnotic music begins]
Hey Chris.
[phone ringing]
[message alert]
- Christopher!
- Mom!
The nanny cam!
The... The nanny cam, wha...
It's fine. I'm
right here with Mikey.
You're on the nanny cam.
Is this live? Is...
what's happening?
I...I can see you.
At first I thought you were
scratching yourself
and then I saw that...
- With your son right there.
- [phone ringing]
What the fuck, Chris?
Yeah, so I'm
guessing you saw that.
Yes, I saw. I opened it in front
of like five fucking people.
I just had a moment of weakness.
Watching porn
in front of our kid?
It wasn't porn.
It was Instagram.
Instagram? Wait, what?
To someone we knew?
- No, no one we know.
- Oh my god.
It was Charlisse, wasn't it?
- It wasn't Charlisse.
- You guys,
You guys, it's fine.
I'll be right back.
- It's just... I'll be right...
- Okay...
[Charlisse] Hang up on him!
You know that I know
that you like--
Okay...
every one of
her photos and videos, right?
She is your friend
and my best friend's ex.
I'm just trying
to keep things civil.
Oh really civil,
trying to turn my friend
- into your fuck fantasy.
- Okay look...
I'm sorry
that the fact that my body...
Had to make another body
changed some things about me.
Okay, you're drunk.
I'm not drunk.
What's finally clear to me
is you have been checked out
for years.
I did pregnancy alone.
You were too busy working.
And then
that fell apart. And then?
And then you were too depressed
to change a fucking diaper.
That is not fair.
I don't want to stay on this
dysfunctional merry-go-round
with you
and then get off
when it's too late.
That is the mistake
that my mom made,
and I am not
- gonna make the same mistake.
- There it is.
God, everything is so black
and white with you.
I am so sorry.
Okay? I'm sorry I'm not
some great businessman.
Or a romance
novel husband. Okay?
I am trying my best, Charlisse.
Did you just call me Charlisse?
I have no idea
where that came from. I...
They both start with "“Shar."”
Oh my god. I can't.
You brought her up.
No Chris,
you brought her up on your phone
so you could get up
your fucking limp dick.
No, don't...
God!
[app alert]
[message alert]
Oh god, dude.
Face-Timing me
is Russian roulette,
you know that.
Anyway, it's just a piss.
I didn't know
you were a piss-sitter.
Charlisse fucking
stood in some one night.
Her fault because she wouldn't
let me get that fucking urinal.
And uh... I never stood again.
Now I kind of dig it.
Sharon saw me jerking it
on the baby monitor.
Wow.
Yowza.
And for some odd reason,
she thought I was...
Looking at your ex-wife.
Well, that's understandable.
But Jesus. Did
you have to broadcast it?
Well I broadcasted
it to my mom. So there's that.
- I'm actually speechless.
- [message alert]
Is this what it's
like when I call you?
Yeah, except
I experienced that thing.
What's it called?
Shame.
That's the word.
- You gotta fuck her, man.
- Who? Star-Crossed girl?
No, your wife.
- It'll set everything right.
- [message alert]
I can give you Viagra. Make
sure you're tip-top.
Make her feel
like she still got it.
I mean, your wife is hot, bro.
I wouldn't jerk off to her on
a baby monitor,
but she's fucking sexy.
- Okay.
- Just go through the motions.
Dude, I don't want to
go through the motions.
I want to want it.
Yeah.
I'm afraid those
days might be behind us.
[outgoing call ringing]
[Chris] Hey.
[Sharon] I'm
waiting on Charlisse.
We're taking
a Lyft to the hotel.
I'm really sorry,
I...I don't know
what came over me. I just...
I was so embarrassed.
[Sharon] The thing is, I feel
like you're embarrassed by me.
No, don't be ridiculous.
It's like you don't
even think of me as your wife
Or your partner anymore.
It's like I'm... I'm just...
Some appendage.
It's just...
You know,
I want to provide on my own.
I want to be a man, but...
When you got pregnant,
it made me realize...
I'm not.
I'm still just a kid.
A salary doesn't make you a man.
Yeah, I know.
I don't want to
be roommates, okay?
Me neither.
But what do you want?
Do you actually
want me? Do you...
even find me
attractive at all anymore?
Of course I do.
I wish I was
looking at you right now.
I think you're
beautiful inside but...
I'm really into that hot-ass
bod and perfect smile.
Green eyes.
[Sharon] Okay, Mr. Cheeseball.
[phone ringing]
Oh, okay.
Hold on, one second...
Ah, oops
There. How's that?
Ah, very funny.
Turn the filter off.
What filter? What
are you talking about?
You've got something on the...
No, you look lovely honey.
You don't mean that. You...
You really don't mean that.
No, I. I just was...
God, I disgust you.
Don't... That's not...
All right,
Chris. I got to go. Um...
We'll talk this
week or something.
Wait. Wait, calm...
- Wait!
- I don't...
[message alert]
[mysterious music begins]
[call ringing]
[Dr. Zephyr]
Please. If I'm mistaken...
Then this will
only take a second.
[call ringing]
Chris, thank you.
Thank you. I just wanted you
to see it was really me.
I don't know you.
Excuse me for a second,
I have astigmatism, so...
- Okay...
- Night driving is...
a bit challenging.
Um...
Chris, am I correct...
That you met someone online
in the last few hours?
That's...
Why do you want to know?
This contact...
was it of a sexual nature?
Whoa, dude.
Okay. Um...
It's lucky
that I'm somewhat close.
I'm driving down
from San Jose right now.
- Wait, what?
- Chris,
what you're engaging in
is very, very dangerous.
You understand?
Were you speaking with a woman?
I'm assuming you are...
You're a heterosexual?
Okay, I'm.
I'm going to hang up.
Listen, I'm asking
you, please don't engage
with this woman any
further until I arrive, okay?
I triangulated
your cell phone towers.
I should
be within blocks of you in--
Dude, what the hell?
This is fucking weird.
You don't have to give me
your address, Chris, okay?
I mean, we can...
We can meet any way you like.
I mean, even in a public place.
I just. I just.
I just need for
you to understand, all right?
It's a dangerous situation
you're in,
and I'm just here to help.
I think maybe we could even...
Help each other.
Chris, you there?
Chris, you need to stay awake.
I was just reading up on you.
Um...
Well, that's not um...
I understand. I mean...
probably looks... troubling.
It was Adra, wasn't it?
Adra?
Is that the name
it gave you? It...
How do you spell that?
Why? So
you can keep stalking her?
No, no, no. You're
conflating two different--
What the fuck did you do to her?
You did something
to her face, didn't you?
You saw her face?
A picture?
Was it a video
call like this one?
Okay, I'm calling the cops.
If you get
anywhere near either of us--
Chris, Chris. You have
jumped to too many
understandable but wrong conclusions.
I mean, this Adra woman.
She was never my student.
She's--
Goddammit.
Chris, don't hang up--
[call ringing]
Hey, you.
Hey.
You got your voice back.
[message alert]
I'm still a little weak, but
feeling a lot better.
That's good.
Yeah, um...
So this guy...
Dr. Zephyr just messaged me.
Somehow knows
we've been talking.
Do you know him?
Adra, you can tell me.
I want to help.
[message alert]
What did this guy do to you?
I thought you were coming.
I said maybe.
Just now,
you said you were coming.
On Star-Crossed.
On Star-Crossed?
Adra...
Listen, this wasn't me.
What?
Zephyr.
The guy must've
hacked my account.
No, no.
Did you give him your address?
- I thought he was you.
- Fuck!
Don't be mad.
You should leave.
I can't leave. I'm hurt.
Okay, you can walk, right?
You can go
somewhere, to a neighbor.
You should come.
Come pick me up.
I can't. I have the baby.
I'm scared.
What the fuck did this guy do?
Please, Chris. Please.
[message alert]
I'm going to call the police.
No.
No, you can't call them.
No, I think it's what's best.
- That will be worse for me.
- [message alert]
Please.
Just give me a sec.
Okay?
Don't go.
I have an idea.
Okay, I'll be right back...
No! No--
[message alert]
[outgoing call ringing]
Come on.
[message alert]
[foreign speakers]
[goats bleating]
[foreign shouting]
[ripping sounds]
[timer beeps]
[Eddie] Hey, uh,
- can't really talk right now.
- [driving sounds]
Hey man, um...
I think there's something weird
going on with this girl.
Do you think maybe you can come
over here and watch Mikey
while I go over there?
You need
a booty call babysitter?
No, it's this
guy, her professor.
I think he hacked my account
and gone over there, huh?
Huh? Professor? What?
Yeah this guy, Zephyr. Uh...
He called me.
He knows Adra, and...
I think he's
the one who hurt her.
And then I saw my star crossed
account was open,
- and so I thought maybe he was--
- Oh, no, sorry, man.
That was me.
Wait? You hacked my account?
I didn't "“hack"” it.
I knew you had a couple
old passwords
that you use
for BS accounts like that.
So you just went in?
What the hell, man?
You said you weren't
going to see this chick.
There wasn't a link in
the account that I matched with,
so I thought I'd do some
research.
See if I could
meet up with her.
Dude.
What? You were
dealing with your shit.
So I figured I'd
deal with my shit.
Just break into my account?
You just created it today.
I didn't think it would be
that big of a deal.
Okay, she doesn't
want you. She wants me.
[laughs] Oh, I didn't know
we were trying to get our little
Pee-Wee Herman wet.
I'm not. It's
the principle of the thing, man.
I get a vibe
off of her, alright?
God...
Something about
how vulnerable she is.
Gets all the blood, like,
telling me to just
pass my seed
onto this young creature
Dude, what the fuck?
Okay, you can't pass your
seed onto anybody, okay?
Your count is too low.
Man, fuck you for saying that.
Look I am not
trying to do that--
I told you that in confidence
and you throw it back in
my face?
If you go over there pretending
to be me, it could be like a
like a sex crime, okay?
False advertising.
"“False advertising?"”
This chick
doesn't even know you.
She calls you Christopher
for Christ's sake.
Your mom named you that,
she doesn't even fucking call
you that.
Okay, it's called
rape by deception, man.
All right?
What? Did you just
Google that?
Yes, cause I'm
looking out for you.
I'm not going to lie to
the chick or,
like, make her do anything
she doesn't want to do.
It's up to her.
Dude, I know you
won't admit this,
but drinking turns
you into a total scumbag,
even by your own standards.
Yeah? Well, I'm not the one
who's trying to cheat on
his wife.
Because you are divorced!
Yeah, and my ex is probably
out there
looking for a low cost
sperm donor
And guess what? Your wife
is right there with her.
Fuck you, man. All right?
If our friendship means
anything to you,
you will turn around now.
[driving sounds]
Fine.
You don't want me to go?
I won't go.
Thank you.
Jesus.
So you think maybe you could
come over here and watch Mikey--
Oh fuck off!
[foreign language]
[goats bleating]
[squishy sounds]
[foreign language]
[crunching, squishy sounds]
[foreign shouting]
[ominous music plays]
[coughs]
- Oh, Jesus. Fuck.
- [baby cries]
[harsh breathing, baby crying]
[foreign shouting]
- Oh, Jesus.
- [stabbing sounds]
- [baby shrieking]
[kettle whistling]
[incoming call ringing]
A car just drove by.
I think it's him.
I think it's Dr. Zephyr.
That guy's sick but it's not him
But I gave him the address.
That was my idiot friend Eddie.
He's the one who hacked
my account, not Zephyr.
So Dr. Zephyr is not coming?
No. And neither is Eddie.
Please come.
I'm feeling good.
You make me feel good.
Look.
This is all too weird.
I don't know you.
I don't know
Zephyr and the video...
I'm fucking sick.
I'll make you feel better.
Maybe another time.
This is just too fucking weird.
I should get off.
Shhh, baby.
It's okay.
Try to be calm.
Close your eyes, come on.
[Adra] Isn't that better?
[Adra] Don't I make
you feel better?
[Chris] Yeah.
[Chris] Actually you do.
[Adra] You can relax.
[Adra] Let's just talk online.
[Adra] The next best thing.
Do you have a candle?
Somewhere, yeah.
You're so stressed, baby.
You need to relax.
You deserve it.
You're a good person.
I know these things.
Go get a candle, trust me.
Don't light it just yet.
Turn off your lights.
Lights dim.
There.
Now it doesn't hurt my eyes.
Wow.
I love your eyes.
They really like that?
Yes.
They're so sensitive.
But I want to see you.
I want you to see me.
You're so handsome.
- Come on.
- It's true.
Don't be silly.
Do you want to kiss me?
Uh what?
Like this.
Come close.
Here.
[kisses air]
You missed me, silly.
Closer.
[kissing sound]
Mmm.
That's nice.
And here.
[kissing sound]
Mmm.
Would you like to see my room?
Sure.
Good, baby.
Follow me.
Take my hand.
Just reach out.
Your hands are so sweaty.
Yeah, they are.
Are you nervous?
I guess I am.
Don't be, baby.
Trust me.
Stay right there, baby.
I'm going to light
a few more candles.
Why don't you light yours?
[gasps, heavy breathing]
[ominous whooshing]
Give me your hand.
[belt unbuckling]
I can feel you.
I want you.
You can fill me up.
You can make me whole.
Oh.
You feel so good.
You're perfect.
You're so perfect.
Do you like me?
Yes.
I like you.
Do you want me?
So much.
I want you so much.
Do you love me?
Oh.
Yes, I love you.
I love you so much.
Be a part of me.
Yes, yes.
Inside me forever.
Oh, fuck. Yes.
Inside you forever.
Oh.
Ha.
Ha!
[heavy breathing]
Hey.
Adra?
[strange echoes]
Hey, what is this?
Hello?
Adra?
Fuck...
[distorted echoes]
I'm in here!
I'm trapped!
Wha...
What the fuck?
What the fuck? What the fuck?
What the fuck is happening?
[phone ringing]
Hello? Hello? Hello?
[Dr. Zephyr] I told you not to
keep talking with her,
Christopher.
What the fuck did you do?
You've been
tricked. Do you understand?
She manipulated you.
What is happening?
Alright, first thing,
I'm speaking to you.
I mean, is it via phone?
Yes, of course a fucking phone.
You called me.
Just remember
I called your phone.
Now this is proof of that.
The fact that we're talking.
I'm going insane.
You're not going insane.
Just stay with me, okay?
Now let me ask you,
were you asleep before
this happened?
No.
Were you, um,
engaged in
sexual intercourse with it?
With? No, we met online.
Well, before you said you
saw part of its face.
What was her physical state
when you guys met?
I didn't,
we just... We video chatted.
Christopher.
I just need for you
to be very truthful with me now.
[Chris] Okay, I...
I was jerking off
and she was on the screen.
She got you through...
Through the computer?
The fuck is happening?
Through masturbation,
that's fascinating...
Fuck you, it's fascinating.
Where were you
when you had cybersex with her?
Were you in your room?
- [baby sounds echo]
- Mikey.
My baby.
His mom's not
coming home tonight.
Christopher,
just try to remain calm, okay?
Where were
you before you were here?
Wake up.
- Wake the fuck up!
- Christopher.
There's still
time. I can help you.
You said you weren't asleep.
Were you in an altered state?
What do you mean, altered state?
Did you take
drugs? Hallucinogens?
Okay, so it's
just a hallucination.
Not the way you mean.
She entrances her victims while
they're in a receptive state.
Sex, dreams.
Perhaps while masturbating
your imagination was--
How the fuck does that help me?
Now, since you didn't have
physical contact with her,
There may still be a chance
to get you back but...
You need to do
exactly what I say.
Okay? Now...
Tell me where you were.
Um...
In my house, at my table.
Okay, good.
Now I want you to focus.
Just look at a wall, right?
Look at the blank
wall where the door was.
I'm looking.
Now listen carefully.
I want you to
look through the wall.
Can you do that for me?
No, it's a wall.
It's solid.
Unfocus your eyes.
Now, look through the wall.
- Are you doing it?
- Yes.
Okay, listen carefully.
The physical
you is not in the room.
You are still in your house.
No, I'm in this fucking room.
Your body is
still in your house.
You just need to
find your way back.
Think of it as a neighborhood
with streets in the front and
alleyways in the back.
Or maybe you even want
to think of it as like a sewer.
Just have to find your way back
through the pipes.
What the fuck? A sewer?
Just look.
You're sitting at your desk,
you're looking at the screen.
Just look through your eyes,
your eyes at your table.
What the fuck?
I see it.
Just try to focus on--
How the fuck is this...
But if...
I'm there...
Then that means...
No.
No, no, no.
Fuck, I had it.
I had it!
[phone ringing]
[Dr. Zephyr] Christopher?
Christopher, you there?
How?
The phone vanished.
You realized you've
never had it in the first place.
Okay.
Yeah, but I saw it.
I saw my house.
What matters now
is waking you up, okay?
Now I can do that
but I need your address.
Okay, yeah, it's um...
It's, uh, 750 Coolidge Drive.
Okay, I'm maybe thirty away.
Is there a security system?
Yeah. 3369 shuts it off.
No pound sign
or anything like that?
No, just 3369.
Wait, how did you call me?
Just try to wake up, okay?
- Try unfocusing your eyes.
- Okay...
I can't. It's like trying to
sleep when you're anxious.
Or take a piss
when someone's watching.
Or get hard when
your wife's asking you
why you're not fully
fucking hard and the baby--
And you don't want to
fucking do this anymore.
Okay, okay, let's just try to...
Close your eyes.
Just close them
and think of home.
When you open them you'll
be back in your house, okay?
Deep breaths.
Home.
[tranquil music begins]
[wind sounds]
[Chris]
I can see.
- I can see out through my eyes.
- [incoming call rings]
[Chris laughs]
[Dr. Zephyr] What?
What is it?
[Chris] I told him not to go.
He was so pissed
I probably saved his life.
[message alert]
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
[Dr. Zephyr] What? What?
[Chris] My friend
is outside her place.
[Dr. Zephyr] No!
He absolutely must not go in.
Do you understand?
He must not go in.
[Chris] He's calling.
[Dr. Zephyr] Answer him.
[Chris] I can't.
[Dr. Zephyr] Answer him now!
[call connects]
Eddie!
She's dangerous.
Hey, Chris.
I think you're frozen.
She's dangerous!
I can barely hear you, buddy.
Fuck...
Eddie please!
Turn around!
I feel good about it.
[distorted]
Eddie, she'll kill you!
I feel good.
- Eddie, please.
- Look, I know you're mad.
You'll understand, I promise.
- Eddie!
- I just need this.
- Leave! Go!
- If I can experience this love,
I can set everything else aside.
Get Charlisse back...
Do the whole dad thing
even if it's not really mine.
- Eddie, she'll kill you!
- It's not about sex.
It's about becoming myself
for the first time.
- I want you to understand that.
- Eddie, go home.
You're my best friend.
- Eddie please, turn around.
- My only real friend.
Please!
Stop!
I love you, man.
Eddie, she'll hurt you!
No, no.
[ominous sounds and music]
- [knocking]
- [door creaking open]
Hello?
[hissing sound]
[flies buzzing]
Eddie...
[footsteps echo]
[ominous choir]
[distant shrieking]
Hi, Adra.
[eerie] Hi, Eddie.
You look beautiful.
Thank you.
So do you.
Come see me.
No one understands you.
Do they?
No one.
Not even your wife.
Your ex-wife.
No.
You work so hard for them.
Always making them laugh.
Always taking on their pain.
Never showing your own.
Never.
You're so sensitive.
So beautiful.
Thank you.
You understand.
I see you, Eddie.
I'm the only one who sees you.
Yes.
Do you want to see me too?
So much.
My body isn't
very beautiful right now.
It is.
I'll think it is.
I'm scared to show you.
Please.
Please, I want to see.
Okay.
Okay, you can look.
Thank you.
Oh, God. Thank you.
[slimy squishy sounds]
Oh my god.
Oh my god. You're so beautiful.
Do you like me?
Oh, yes.
Yes, fuck.
We're going to
turn a lock, you and I.
You're my key.
We're going to open a lock...
That hasn't been
open in a thousand years.
Oh yes.
Adra, Adra.
Oh my god.
Yes.
Yes, Eddie.
You're mine, Eddie.
Oh god.
You're all mine.
Oh yes.
Oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Ah.
Ah!
I'm sorry, Eddie.
Oh...
I thought you'd
have more to give.
Oh, no, no!
Ah!
Sorry, baby.
Agh!
Aghhhh!
No!
Eddie, no. God...
[Dr. Zephyr]
Chris, I'm almost there.
Pulling off the freeway.
Chris, just stay calm, okay?
Two minutes.
I don't have two minutes.
[growling]
Feed Mikey.
Take care of my baby.
Tell his mom...
No, no, no, no, no, no!
[screams]
[front door opens]
[heavy footsteps]
[baby cries]
[eerie drone]
Chris if you can hear me.
I'm sorry.
It's too late.
[distant] What?
She chose you, I don't know why.
No.
Stop!
No, wait.
The brain stem.
Immediate, painless.
[door opens]
Um hey, I really think
that we need to talk about...
[baby crying]
Seriously?
Okay.
[baby crying]
Sharon!
[sighs]
Hey.
We need to talk.
Hello? Chris.
Chris?
Hey, honey. Honey?
Hey, babe.
Babe?
What did you,
did you take something?
Shit.
Hi. Yes.
Hi, yeah, I need
an ambulance right away.
My husband, I think, um,
I think he's had a stroke.
Yeah. Okay.
- [gust of wind]
- Yeah, I'll stay on the line.
[creaking]
[suspenseful music begins]
Um...
Yes, one second.
Let me just get a pen.
There's a burglar.
There's a burglar in the house.
Ah!
[tussling]
Tell them it's fine.
Tell them it was
a misunderstanding.
Um...
Never mind. False alarm.
Tell them it was the neighbor.
It was the neighbor. The...
neighbor's dog got in.
Hang up.
They said they were coming.
They said they're on their way.
No they didn't.
Take whatever you want.
Nothing's worth anything.
We spent it all on the house.
[phone ringing]
That's them.
I have to answer this.
Quiet!
I'm trying to think.
[phone ringing]
Yeah.
Could be a murder suicide.
Wait. No, no, listen.
I don't understand
what you're saying.
For the greater good.
I'm sorry.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Hi, baby.
I've missed you.
You can't hurt me.
Not yet.
[Adra, demonic]
I don't want to hurt you.
I love you.
I want you.
They're just a path in.
You have to let me in.
No.
[inaudible]
You could be so great, honey.
Let me help you.
[electricity surges]
Is that it?
You're still too weak.
But she's getting stronger.
No.
Go.
Help her.
No, I have a baby, please...
You don't understand.
You don't know
why I have to do this.
No, I don't
understand, please...
I'll make it quick.
Please...
Wait, please don't...
I swear...
I won't hurt your baby.
[gasps]
[pained groan]
[gasping for air]
Good, baby. Good.
Good...
He's infected.
He'll kill us all.
Stop. Don't take another step.
Look at him.
Look what's
already happened to him.
Stay back.
She's inside of him.
Stay back. Stop.
She's only gonna get stronger.
Stop!
She's going to use him.
She's going to use both of you.
She'll impregnate you...
Shut the fuck up.
If you knew what I knew
you'd take that gun and
you'd shoot him right now.
I'm warning you.
Safety's on.
[gunshot]
[pained grunt]
[heavy breaths]
Okay.
W...wait...
Hey, don't move. Don't move!
[door opens]
[door closes]
Chris, Chris...
Chris?
Where did you go?
I love you. I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry we fought.
I'm so sorry.
Please, just come back...
You're going to be
okay. You're going to be okay.
Please be okay.
Chris.
Chris?
Wh...
Where did you go?
I'm...
I'm home.
[baby crying]
[tranquil music]
[message alert]
Oh, shit.
[scary sounds rise]
Hey, Chris.
Chris, you okay?
Chris?
Oh, oh.
Hey.
[ominous choir builds]
Hey...
[surprised gasp]
[gasp]
[belt unbuckling]
I missed you.
It's like missing a part of me.
Do you feel it?
Yes.
I'm inside you.
Between your cells.
In the space that's nobody.
Nothing.
You have good cells, Chris.
You know that?
Yes.
You know
who else has good cells?
My wife.
Yes.
Your wife.
She's strong
Hey, stay with me.
And your wife's
friend, Charlisse.
I got a taste of
her through Eddie.
Poor Eddie's
cells were not so good.
[Eddie's scream echoes]
Hey.
Hey, are you okay?
[distant] Sharon!
Be a good boy, now.
[echoes] Be a good boy, now.
We'll make so many.
As many as we need.
Until we have the right one.
No, no, no.
Yes.
Yes, yes.
Ah!
Uh.
Huh.
[Adra, distant] Do you like me?
Do you love me?
Sharon.
Run!
Chris, wha...
Chris...
[surprised gasp]
Stop!
Chris!
[slicing sounds]
[splattering sounds]
[glass shatters]
[screams]
Oh, oh.
[gasps]
No.
I'm still a part of you.
[choking sounds]
I'll always be a part of you.
[gasps]
What did you do?
I did it.
I stopped her.
Oh, my god. Oh, my god.
I love you.
So much.
My Sharona.
- My Sharona.
- Chris!
[chopping sound]
[silence]
[birds chirping]
[door opens]
[Denise] Hi.
Hi, how are you?
- Hi...
How are you doing?
- It's good to see you.
- Hi.
Charlisse, you're looking well.
Oh, thank you. So do you.
So is...
Is Mikey up?
Oh, I just put him down. Sorry.
Oh.
There's my boy.
Hi, honey.
How are you today?
I never thought
this beard suited him.
Can we just?
Well, he liked the beard.
Charlisse, do
you think the beard suits him?
Oh, I um...
Oh, are you thirsty?
Can I get you a drink? Water?
No, no, no.
Don't trouble yourself.
Okay.
Well, then um...
We have
something that we would...
Love to talk to you about...
They found that psycho.
That crazy man
that tried to kill my son.
- No, no.
- No.
Well not... Not yet.
Um...
No, today
we wanted to talk about...
As you know, the surgeon was not
able to reattach his...
Yes.
I'm aware.
They were... Um...
Well, I requested that they...
Extract some of his...
Oh...
So um...
About three months ago...
I went to the clinic and...
Well...
I'm pregnant.
Oh.
Oh this is...
This is...
Wonderful.
Oh, yes.
- I'm so glad...
- Why would you think that I'd--?
Wait, wait.
Here, look, look, look.
[ominous music plays]
Oh, my God.
Look.
This is beautiful. Wha...
Why would
you think I would be angry?
Well, um...
- Well, there's...
- Um...
Just... More.
- Right.
So...
Charlisse's husband...
- Or ex.
- Ex...
- Ex. Um.
- Husband.
Passed away.
Poor Eddie.
Well, we had been
trying before and were
considering a donor
anyway, so we thought...
Well, since neither, um...
Child would
have a father present,
That at least they'd have
a brother or a sister.
[ultrasound heartbeat]
Oh.
Oh, my God.
This is a miracle.
I mean, this is a miracle.
Yeah.
Two grandchildren, babies.
I never thought
I would feel this happy again.
I'm so happy to
hear you say that.
Thank you, Mrs. Johnson.
Honey, did you hear that?
Christopher, look.
You're going to be
a father again and again.
These are your babies.
This is so incredible.
I can't wait to meet them.
They are so perfect.
Perfect little angels.
[ultrasound heartbeats]
[Adra] Hey Chris...
[heavy metal music]
Evil